University Relations Records
University of Houston Libraries
University Relations Records
1971-1997
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
Universityof Houston--Office of University Relations
28.00 Linear Feet
The Office of University Relations along with the Office of Development comprises the Division of University Advancement, which works to advance the institution both externally and internally. The Office of University Relations supports the university through the offices of internal and external communications, publications, and marketing. The Office of External Communications generates communications pieces, such as news releases to the media, and responses to media inquiries on behalf of the university. The collection dates from 1948-1997 with most of the materials dating from 1977 to 1997.
1997-016
Historical Note
The Office of University Relations along with the Office of Development comprises the Division of University Advancement, which works to advance the institution both externally and internally. The Office of University Relations supports the university through the offices of internal and external communications, publications, and marketing. The Office of External Communications generates communications pieces, such as news releases to the media, and responses to media inquiries on behalf of the university. Its goal is to ensure information about the university and its colleges is communicated accurately and timely to the public via the news media, both local and beyond. The Office of Internal Communications disseminates major university news and events to faculty, staff and students. The Office of University Marketing seeks to enhance the University of Houston's efforts to bolster the image of the university.
Scope and Contents
The collection arrived at the archives in relatively good order and in general the original order has been maintained. Materials in the collection include departmental records, extensive press clippings, and videos. The collection dates from 1948-1997 with most of the materials dating from 1977 to 1997. The collection is organized into four series: Faculty Vitas, Departmental Records, Press Clippings, and Audio Visual Materials. The collection did contain a sizable amount of photographic materials in all formats (slides, negatives, prints, contact sheets, etc), that have been separated to form the UH Historic Photographs Collection. The Office of University Relations also contained a large number of faculty vitas that were transferred to the Faculty Vita Records: 1969-066.
Index Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
University of Houston--Office of University Relations; University of Houston
Genre/Form of Material:
Administrative records; Clippings; Videocassettes
Topical Term:
University of Houston-- Faculty
Access Restrictions
Open for research.
Acquisition
Transferred from Office of University Relations.
Detailed Description
- Departmental Records
  This series contains one hundred and seventy-four folders, arranged alphabetically. It consists of City Council Awards given to faculty members, annual reports, reports to the community and various other files used within the department. Materials in this series date from 1948-1997 and are arranged alphabetically.
  - Achievements, Faculty, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advertising Campaign, Faculty, 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Advertisement, UH, 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Afro-American for Black Liberation, (AABL), March 1966- February1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AABL (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AABL (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AABL - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report, 1982-83 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1983-84 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report, 1984-85 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report, 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report Narratives, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report Narratives (continued) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Architecture Building, 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Athletics, 1988-89 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Athletics, (continued), 1988-89 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Block, Farris - Thesis, "The Newspaper,", 1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Block, Farris - Thesis: "The Newspaper,", 1963 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Block, Farris - Thesis: "The Newspaper,", 1963 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Broadcast Station Information (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Building Program - UH, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - City Council Awards, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - City Council Awards, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - City Council Awards, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - City Council Awards, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Clear Lake City Information (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - College of Business Administration, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Commencement Address - TSU, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Communication Plan, 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Communication Plan, 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Communication Plan, 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Communication Plan, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Communication Plan Funding, 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Communication Plan Funding, 1987-88 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Communications, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Communication Department, 1969-70 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Communication Department (continued), 1969-70 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Convocation, Autumn, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cullen Performance Hall, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Cullen Program Copy, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Program, May 16, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Programs, May 15, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Convocations and Receptions Programs (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Convocations and Receptions Programs, August, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Convocations and Receptions Programs, May 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Convocations and Receptions Programs, May 10, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Convocations and Receptions Programs, May 16, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Dale, Dr. E.E. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Department Chairman Conference, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Department Chairman's Conference, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Department Chairman's Conference, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Department Chairman's Conference, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Department Chairman's Conference, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Department Chairman's Conference, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Dirty Works (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - "E" Awards, 1964-66 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - "E" Awards (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Downtown College Information, 1973-74 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Economic Summit Meeting, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Economic Summit Meeting, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Economic Summit Party, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Fraternities, 1969-73 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Gazette (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Goals and Objectives, 1985-91 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - HCPRSA Newsletters, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - HCPRSA Newsletters, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - HCPRSA Postage Receipts, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - HCPRSA Correspondence, 1968-69 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - HCPRSA Newsletters, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - HCPRSA Newsletter, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - HCPRSA By Laws, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - HCPRSA Correspondence, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - HCPRSA Chapter Meeting Attendance Cards (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - HCPRSA Dues (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - HCPRSA Membership (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - HCPRSA Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Highlights, UH, September, 1984, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Highlights, UH, 1989-90 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Hoffman, Dr. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Honor's Day, April 30, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Honor's Day, April 30, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Honor's Day, April 30, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Honor's Day Convocation, April 30, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Honor's Day Convocation Program, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Honor's Day Convocation Program, April 27, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Human Resources, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Inaugural Certificate, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Inaugural Certificate, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Inaugural Certificate, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Institutional Communication Plan, 1986-87 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Legislative Communication Plan, 1988-89 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Legislative Issues, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Legislative Priorities, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Legislative Priorities, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Mascot, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Media Mailing Lists (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - National Rankings, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Newspaper - Student Unrest, 1967-69 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - News Service Annual Report, August 1953 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - News Service Annual Report, 1953-54 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Organizational Charts - Section I, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Organizational Charts - Section II, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Organizational Charts - Section III, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Organizational Charts - Section IV, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Organizational Charts - Section V, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Organizational Charts - Section VI, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Organizational Charts - Section VII, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Photographs (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Planning, UH, 1988-89 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Planning, UH, 1990-95 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Plans, Policies, Regulations, November 1969-October 1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Plans, Policies, Regulations, May 1974-May 1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - President's Office, 1985-96 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - President's Office/MRB Bridge Program (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - President's Office/Reading File, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - President's Office/Reading File, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - President's Office/Reading File: Benefits, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases, February 1966-February 1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Press Release, March- June 1969 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Preliminary Plans for Central College of Nursing (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Pride, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Pride, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Pride, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Programs Handbooks (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Proposed Programs, 1951/52 - 1954/55 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Proposed Programs, 1955-56 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Public Relations Objectives, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Public Relations Programs, 1961-62 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Public Relations Programs, 1965-66 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Publications Six-Year Plan, 1983-89 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Public Relations Report- School of Technology, Fall 1948 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Public Relations Report - School of Technology, Spring 1949 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Public Relations Report - School of Technology, Summer 1949 (copy) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Public Relations Report - School of Technology, Fall 1949 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Public Relations Report - School of Technology, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Public Relations Report, 1950-51 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Public Relations Report, Spring 1951 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Public Relations Report, 1951-52 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Public Relations and Development Meeting, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Public Relations Report, 1952-53 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Public Relations Report, 1953-54 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Public Relations Report, 1954-55 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "Rain of Gold", 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Report to the Community, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Report to the Community, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Report to the Community, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Report to the Community, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Report to the Community, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Science and Research III (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Senior Vice President, 1989-95 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Sigma Delta Chi, 1950-1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Sigma Delta Chi, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Sigma Delta Chi, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Silver Anniversary, August 1956 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Social Sciences/Center for Public Policy, 1985-87 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Special Events Commencement, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Special Events Information (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Speeches (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Staff Publications (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Strategic Communication Planning, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Strides, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Twenty-five Year Anniversary, UH and US Space Program, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - UH Foundations (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - UH Foundations, 1974-75 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - UH Magazine, 1994-95 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - UH Newspaper Clippings (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - UH Officials, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - UH Students, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Victoria Center Information (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Woodland Information (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Your Hometown News Houston Post Series (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Building Dedications
  This series contains twenty-seven folders dating from 1977-1980, arranged alphabetically. The folders contain materials including invitations, guest lists, receipts, memos, and other items related to the preparations necessary for these events. The original order has been maintained except where items were obviously miss-filed.
  - Anderson Library, Freeman Wing, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Anderson Library, Freeman Wing, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Anderson Library, Freeman Wing, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Student Center, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - College of Business, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - College of Optometry (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - College of Optometry, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - College of Optometry, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - College of Optometry, Building Invitation List (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - College of Pharmacy, Texas Medical Center, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - College of Pharmacy, Texas Medical Center, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - College of Technology, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Communications Building, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Communications Building, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Communications Building, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cullen Performance Hall, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cullen Performance Hall, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Cullen Performance Hall, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Graduate School of Social Work, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Graduate School of Social Work, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Graduate School of Social Work, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Graduate School of Social Work, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Graduate School of Social Work, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Graduate School of Social Work, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Hoffman Hall, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Houston Science Center, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Plagues (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Wortham Theatre, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- In Memoriam
  In Memoriam are arranged alphabetically, according to the last name of the individual. Each record contains information (education, birth and death dates, place of birth, and positions held) for faculty, staff, and benefactors, associated with the university.
  - John Q. Anderson (Box 8, Item 1)
  - Mrs. Agnes Louise Cullen Arnold (Box 8, Item 2)
  - Isaac Arnold (Box 8, Item 3)
  - Anthony Andrew Aucoin (Box 8, Item 4)
  - Charles A. Bacarisse (Box 8, Item 5)
  - Light D'Albergo Bailey (Box 8, Item 6)
  - James V. Baker (Box 8, Item 7)
  - Hallie Logan Trout Barrow (Box 8, Item 8)
  - Colonel William B. Bates (Box 8, Item 9)
  - Ben Belt (Box 8, Item 10)
  - Joyce Benbrook (Box 8, Item 11)
  - Randolph Blumberg (Box 8, Item 12)
  - Albert James Bonar, Sr (Box 8, Item 13)
  - Harold R. Bottrell (Box 8, Item 14)
  - Julian B. Brandes (Box 8, Item 15)
  - Andrew David Bruce (Box 8, Item 16)
  - Mrs. George A. (Anne Garrett) Butler (Box 8, Item 17)
  - Dorothy Hinds Callicutt (Box 8, Item 18)
  - Laurie T. Callicutt (Box 8, Item 19)
  - Rudolph J. Capobianco (Box 8, Item 20)
  - Americo Castro (Box 8, Item 21)
  - Albert Louis Chovanec (Box 8, Item 22)
  - James P. Clements (Box 8, Item 23)
  - Dr. Juanita Luck Cogan (Box 8, Item 24)
  - Mrs. Jullie Cranz Cullen (Box 8, Item 25)
  - Mr. Hugh Roy Cullen (Box 8, Item 26)
  - Lester J. Dewald (Box 8, Item 27)
  - Milton B. Dobrin (Box 8, Item 28)
  - Helen M. Douthitt (Box 8, Item 29)
  - James T. Duke (Box 8, Item 30)
  - Victor F. Dunlap (Box 8, Item 31)
  - Stephen Power Farish (Box 8, Item 32)
  - Curtis L. Farrington (Box 8, Item 33)
  - Gabriel A. Fazekas (Box 8, Item 34)
  - Clare Evelyn Knowles Fleming (Box 8, Item 35)
  - Lamar Fleming Jr (Box 8, Item 36)
  - Lawrence E. Freeman (Box 8, Item 37)
  - Larry W. Fultz (Box 8, Item 38)
  - Eugene P. Goldschmidt (Box 8, Item 39)
  - Hubert Goodwin, Jr. (Box 8, Item 40)
  - Robert L. Grainger (Box 8, Item 41)
  - Marjorie Dolores Green (Box 8, Item 42)
  - Penrose W. Hirst (Box 8, Item 43)
  - John E. Hoff (Box 8, Item 44)
  - Martha Gano Houstoun (Box 8, Item 45)
  - Jack Dupree Hunter (Box 8, Item 46)
  - Harry A. Jankiewicz (Box 8, Item 47)
  - Doyle King Jenkins (Box 8, Item 48)
  - Charles Alexander Johnson (Box 8, Item 49)
  - Halbert H. Johnson (Box 8, Item 50)
  - V. J. Kennedy (Box 9, Item 1)
  - Alva Lee Kerbow (Box 9, Item 2)
  - William Townes Kittinger, Jr. (Box 9, Item 3)
  - Robert W. Kneebone (Box 9, Item 4)
  - David W. Knepper (Box 9, Item 5)
  - Leslie S. G. Kovasznay (Box 9, Item 6)
  - Doris Young Kuhn (Box 9, Item 7)
  - Francis Marion Law (Box 9, Item 8)
  - Donald Lee (Box 9, Item 9)
  - Walter William Lodge (Box 9, Item 10)
  - John Sheridan MacNerney (Box 9, Item 11)
  - Mrs. Mildred Yount Manion (Box 9, Item 12)
  - James Leslie McCary (Box 9, Item 13)
  - Charles Flemming McElhinney (Box 9, Item 14)
  - Laurence Shirley McGaughran (Box 9, Item 15)
  - John McHale (Box 9, Item 16)
  - Amos W. Melton (Box 9, Item 17)
  - Hawkins Menefee (Box 9, Item 18)
  - Edward L. Michaels (Box 9, Item 19)
  - Clifton C. Miller (Box 9, Item 20)
  - Murry A. Miller (Box 9, Item 21)
  - Ruth Morton (Box 9, Item 22)
  - Madelene Louise Bernard Nabor (Box 9, Item 23)
  - Mary Jeanne Treichler Neal (Box 9, Item 24)
  - Mrs. Myrtle May Barr Oberholtzer (Box 9, Item 25)
  - Daniel E. O'Keefe (Box 9, Item 26)
  - Ralph Stacy Page (Box 9, Item 27)
  - Charles Thomas Parker (Box 9, Item 28)
  - Anne Reynolds Phillips (Box 9, Item 29)
  - Henry Martin Rockwell (Box 9, Item 30)
  - Matthew Whiting Rosa ( (Box 9, Item 31)
  - Frank S. Runyon (Box 9, Item 32)
  - Stephen Peter Sakach (Box 9, Item 33)
  - Elmer Schoettle (Box 9, Item 34)
  - Sam Schulman (Box 9, Item 35)
  - Charles Intervale Silin (Box 9, Item 36)
  - Louis Lazarus Silverman (Box 9, Item 37)
  - A. Dee Simpson (Box 9, Item 38)
  - Nann Zetta Slade (Box 9, Item 39)
  - Frank Chesley Smith (Box 9, Item 40)
  - Marvin D. Sterrett (Box 9, Item 41)
  - Osman Orlando Stotts (Box 9, Item 42)
  - Noel Ross Strader (Box 9, Item 43)
  - Charles B. Walker (Box 9, Item 44)
  - Tom P. Walker (Box 9, Item 45)
  - Ronald Wallace Wendahl (Box 9, Item 46)
  - Joseph S. Werlin (Box 9, Item 47)
  - Betty A. Wieland (Box 9, Item 48)
  - Clanton W. Williams (Box 9, Item 49)
  - William Henry Willson (Box 9, Item 50)
  - Hubert L. Wolf (Box 9, Item 51)
  - Gus Sessions Wortham (Box 9, Item 52)
  - Raymond T. Yelkin (Box 9, Item 53)
  - George E Young (Box 9, Item 54)
  - Allyn Zanger (Box 9, Item 55)
- In Appreciation and In Resolutions
  In Appreciation and In Resolutions are arranged alphabetically, according to the last name of the individual. Each record contains information for each person or benefactors associated with the university, and outline the major accomplishments of those persons or entities.
  - William B Bates (Box 10, Item 1)
  - James T. Duke (Box 10, Item 2)
  - George S. Hawn (Box 10, Item 3)
  - William P. Hobby, Jr. (Box 10, Item 4)
  - Philip G. Hoffman (Box 10, Item 5)
  - Edward D. Manion (Box 10, Item 6)
  - Corbin J. Robertson (Box 10, Item 7)
  - Jack Valenti (Box 10, Item 8)
- In Resolution
  In Resolution are arranged alphabetically, according to the last name of the individual or organization. Each record contains information for faculty, staff, and benefactors, associated with the university and outline the major accomplishments of those persons or entities
  - The Attainment of Excellence in the Athletics Program (Box 10, Item 9)
  - Mrs. Sarah Campbell Blaffer (Box 10, Item 10)
  - Andrew Davis Bruce (Box 10, Item 11)
  - The Cullen Foundation (Box 10, Item 12)
  - Thomas J. Dillehay (Box 10, Item 13)
  - Aaron J. Farfel (Box 10, Item 14)
  - Ralph E. Frede (Box 10, Item 15)
  - Dr. and Mrs. Richard J. Gonzalez (Box 10, Item 16)
  - Philip G. Hoffman (Box 10, Item 17)
  - Robert W. Kneebone (Box 10, Item 18)
  - The Max Krost Charitable Trust (Box 10, Item 19)
  - Mrs. Max Levine (Box 10, Item 20)
  - The Moody Foundation (Box 10, Item 21)
  - Welch Foundation (Box 10, Item 22)
- Silver Anniversary Certificates
  Silver Anniversary Certificates are arranged alphabetically, according to the last name of the individual and are divided into three categories; Faculty and Staff, Former Faculty Members, and Recognized Faculty. Each record contains information for faculty and staff associated with the university and outlines the major accomplishments of the individuals.
  - Faculty and Staff
    Individual certificates.
    - Charles F. Hiller (Box 11, Item 1)
    - Louis Kestenberg (Box 11, Item 2)
    - C. F. McElhinney (Box 11, Item 3)
    - L. Standlee Mitchell (Box 11, Item 4)
    - Warren A. Rees (Box 11, Item 5)
    - Lillian Lurille Warren (Box 11, Item 6)
    - Joseph S. Werlin (Box 11, Item 7)
    - Ruth Slater Wikoff (Box 11, Item 8)
  - Former Faculty Members
    S. W. Henderson Floy P. Soule A. W. French E. M. Schuhmann Jules A. Vern M. A. Miller A. L. Kerbow
  - Recognized Faculty
    Frederic Browne Mrs. Bessie Ebaugh Dr. C. F. Hiller Dr. Alva Kerbow Dr. Louis Kestenberg C. F. McElhinney L. Standlee Mitchell Miss Zelda Osborne Warren Rees Mrs. Lillian Warren Dr. Joseph S. Werlin Mrs. Ruth Wikoff
- Press Clippings
  This series contains ninety-one folders dating from 1977-1997, arranged chronologically by month. The articles relate to a variety of university topics including, athletics, special events, awards and many others. However, the amount of informational content within the clippings varies greatly. Some articles are extensive or in-depth in nature where others may include only a brief mention of the university or a direct quote by a faculty member. The original order was chronological which has been maintained except where items were obviously miss-filed.
  - March 1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - April 1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - September 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - December 1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - January 1978 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - February 1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - March 1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - April 1978 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - May 1978 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - June 1978 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - July 1978 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - August 1978 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - September 1978 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - October 1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - October 1978 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - October 1978 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - November 1978 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - December 1978 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - January 1979 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - February 1979 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - March 1979 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - March 1979 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - April 1979 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - May 1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - June 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - July 1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - August 1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - September 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - October 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - November 1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - December 1979 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - April 1980 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - May 1980 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - June 1980 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - July 1980 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - August 1980 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - October 1980 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - November 1980 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - December 1980 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - March 1981 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - May 1981 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - June 1981 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - March 1985 (Box 13, Folder 20)